There's two camps emerging. There's one
that says
>> [music]
>> AI will eliminate
eliminate all our jobs and then the
robots will eat the babies. That's one
camp. And the other camp says, "Wait a
minute. This is going to take us to
Mars. This is going to democratize
education.
>> [music]
>> This is going to advance the cure for
cancer." The way to fuel that is you got
to build more data centers. You don't
have an option. There are dozens of data
center projects in multiple states,
>> [music]
>> Michigan,
Virginia, West Virginia, Tennessee,
Mississippi, Texas. And all of a sudden,
why is it we can't build anything in
America anymore? What's going on there?
And I think that's the question people
are asking.
>> [music]
>> And And what adversary, if any, would
not want us
to
continue to build our compute power,
our defense systems, our advance in
medical, in bioscience, in education,
and rocket science. For me, all roads
lead back to China. We're in a global
competition, in an economic competition,
in a military competition, and certainly
a technological competition. We want to
be the country that has that, for sure.
Uh we don't want the Chinese leading the
charge on that. And you need a lot of
compute power to be able to keep
advancing those models. I think we're at
the same cusp with AI. So, you you don't
try and guess where you're going. You
provide the platform, which is the AI
compute [music] capacity that I'm
building out in Utah. And then you let
technology and innovation
do its thing. And I think over time,
when people realize
the robots are not going to eat the
babies, that this is a good thing for
America. I think they deserve the right
information to form an opinion on, not
propaganda.